<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ANDROID VERSIONS</string>

    <string-array name="androidNames">
        <item>Apple Pie</item>
        <item>Cupcake</item>
        <item>Donut</item>
        <item>Eclair</item>
        <item>FroYo</item>
        <item>Gingerbread</item>
        <item>Honeycomb</item>
        <item>Ice Cream Sandwich</item>
        <item>Jellybean</item>
        <item>KitKat</item>
        <item>Lollipop</item>
        <item>Marshmallow</item>
        <item>Nougat</item>
        <item>Oreo</item>
        <item>Pie</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="androidVersions">
        <item>1.0</item>
        <item>1.5</item>
        <item>1.6</item>
        <item>2.0/2.1</item>
        <item>2.2</item>
        <item>2.3.x</item>
        <item>3.x</item>
        <item>4.0.x</item>
        <item>4.1</item>
        <item>4.4</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>6.0</item>
        <item>7.0</item>
        <item>8.0</item>
        <item>9.0</item>
        <item>10.0</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="androidAPI">
        <item>API 1</item>
        <item>API 3</item>
        <item>API 4</item>
        <item>API 5-7</item>
        <item>API 8</item>
        <item>API 9-10</item>
        <item>API 11-13</item>
        <item>API 14-15</item>
        <item>API 16-18</item>
        <item>API 19-20</item>
        <item>API 21-22</item>
        <item>API 23</item>
        <item>API 24-25</item>
        <item>API 26-27</item>
        <item>API 28</item>
        <item>API 29</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="androidRdate">
        <item>Released:	September 23, 2008</item>
        <item>Released: April 27, 2009</item>
        <item>Released: September 15, 2009</item>
        <item>Released: October 26, 2009</item>
        <item>Released: May 20, 2010</item>
        <item>Released: December 6, 2010</item>
        <item>Released: February 22, 2011</item>
        <item>Released: October 18, 2011</item>
        <item>Released: July 9, 2012</item>
        <item>Released: October 31, 2013</item>
        <item>Released: November 12, 2014</item>
        <item>Released: October 5, 2015</item>
        <item>Released: August 22, 2016</item>
        <item>Released:	August 21, 2017</item>
        <item>Released: August 6, 2018</item>
        <item>Released: September 3, 2019</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info">
        <item>This is the first commercial version of the software, was released on September 23, 2008. The first commercially available Android device was the HTC Dream. </item>
        <item>This is the third version of Android developed by Google, a major platform release deployable to Android-powered handsets starting in April 2009, that is no longer supported.</item>
        <item>This is the fourth version of the open source Android mobile operating system developed by Google that is no longer supported.</item>
        <item>This is a codename of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google and the fifth operating system for Android, and for the no-longer supported versions 2.0 to 2.1.</item>
        <item>This is the sixth version of Android and is a codename of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 2.2 and 2.2.3.</item>
        <item>This is the seventh version of Android, a codename of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google and released in December 2010, for versions that are no longer supported.</item>
        <item>This is the codename for the eighth version of Android, designed for devices with larger screen sizes, particularly tablets. It is no longer supported (newer versions are).</item>
        <item>This is the ninth version of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google.</item>
        <item>This is the tenth version of Android and the codename given to three major point releases of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 4.1 and 4.3.1.</item>
        <item>This is a codename for the Android mobile operating system and the eleventh version of Android. Unveiled on September 3, 2013, KitKat focused primarily on optimizing the operating system for improved performance on entry-level devices with limited resources. </item>
        <item>This is the fifth major version of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google, spanning versions between 5.0 and 5.1.1.</item>
        <item>This s the sixth major version of the Android operating system and the 13th version of Android. </item>
        <item>This is the seventh major version and 14th original version of the Android operating system.</item>
        <item>This is the eighth major release and the 15th version of the Android mobile operating system.</item>
        <item>This is the ninth major release and the 16th version of the Android mobile operating system. It was first released as a developer preview on March 7, 2018, and released publicly on August 6, 2018. </item>
        <item>This is the tenth major release and the 17th version of the Android mobile operating system. It was released on September 3, 2019. </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
